hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨，春季粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装弹簧提示
installment we're going to look at
我们将要看的分期付款
Google cloud and get the Google cloud
谷歌云并获得谷歌云
platform and the support for spring
平台和Spring 支持
cloud and the integration for spring
云与春季整合
cloud and Google cloud all the cops now
云和谷歌云现在所有警察
we're gonna do so as usually by building
我们将照常通过建立
some software we're gonna look at Google
一些我们要看谷歌的软件
cloud which is one of those
云就是其中之一
infrastructures of service platforms
服务平台的基础架构
it's becoming very very compelling I'm
我变得非常引人注目
sure you've no doubt heard about it and
确保您毫无疑问听说过
you've seen some of the amazing news
您已经看到了一些惊人的消息
cases that are tied to it for a lot of
与之相关的案例很多
use cases when it first came out it was
用例第一次出现的时候是
cheaper then AWS right it was really
比AWS便宜，真的
compelling because it was so cheap but
引人注目，因为它是如此便宜，但
now it's just become a full-featured in
现在它已经成为功能齐全的
of itself it's got a whole bunch of
就其本身而言，
things that are compelling and what's a
令人信服的东西是什么
what I think is the interesting about
我认为有趣的是
Google cloud is that a lot of the things
Google Cloud是很多东西
that it does it offered originally sort
它确实提供了最初的排序
of you know white label sort of
你们知道白色标签的那种
rebranded infrastructure that was
更名的基础架构
originally used at Google and as it grew
最初用于Google及其发展
out a lot of that sort of savvy that
有很多这样的精明
awareness that that built-in skill set
意识到内置技能
you know it's still there of course but
你知道它仍然在那里，但是
now there's a whole bunch of things that
现在有一堆东西
have been offered specifically for
专为
customers for customers outside of
客户以外的客户
Google cloud right outside of Google and
Google Cloud就在Google和
so it's not just a repackaging of
所以这不只是重新包装
existing things that they use inside of
他们在其中使用的现有事物
Google but there's also we're into
Google，但也有我们
pricey features and I think that's made
昂贵的功能，我认为
this a really compelling sort of you
这真是一个令人信服的人
know sort of Willy Wonka choco chocolate
知道那种威利旺卡巧克力
factory right you've got this amazing
工厂的权利，你有这个惊人的
compelling mix of things that are unique
引人入胜的独特事物组合
to Google as well as sort of more
给Google以及更多
enterprising more traditional more sort
进取更传统更排序
of commonplace solutions and it's a nice
常见的解决方案，这是一个很好的
to have that mix right you can run also
拥有正确的混音，您还可以运行
to workloads here and of course if using
这里的工作量，当然如果使用
a platform a cloud foundry or kubernetes
云铸造或kubernetes平台
these are things that run nicely on top
这些都是可以很好地运行的东西
of Google Cloud and so we have seen
谷歌云，所以我们已经看到
we've enjoyed a very good partnership
我们享有很好的合作伙伴关系
with Google cloud over pivotal because
与Google Cloud相比至关重要，因为
tons of our customers use Cloud Foundry
我们大量的客户使用Cloud Foundry
on Google cloud so we have here you know
在Google云端上，所以我们在这里
we have storage options they have some
我们有存储选项，他们有一些
unique to Google some just very Commons
Google独有的一些常识
common BigTable datastore fire stores
常见的BigTable数据存储火灾存储
sequel spanner all that kind of stuff we
续集所有这些东西我们
have a different kinds of networking
有不同种类的网络
different kinds of operational tools
不同种类的操作工具
different kinds of development tools
不同种类的开发工具
right and runtime facilities we have big
权利和运行时设施，我们拥有庞大的
data engines I mean all sorts of
数据引擎，我的意思是各种各样的
interesting things here and we can
有趣的事情在这里，我们可以
administer all of this from the portal
从门户网站管理所有这些
certainly or we could use the shell and
当然，或者我们可以使用外壳和
you can install the shell on your local
您可以在本地安装外壳
machine certainly but it's also possible
当然可以，但也有可能
to configure it using this cloud shell
使用此云外壳对其进行配置
which launches in the browser and so you
它会在浏览器中启动，所以您
can see I have already been logged in
可以看到我已经登录
and it's connected to my session if you
它连接到我的会话，如果您
want to use this on your local machine
想要在本地计算机上使用
and you've got the g-cloud command line
并且您有了g-cloud命令行
pre-installed you can just say g-cloud
预装的你可以说g-cloud
like this and then log in alright and
这样，然后登录好，
it'll prompt you to log in you need to
它会提示您登录，您需要
log in to a particular thing here you
在这里登录到特定的东西
cloud maybe it's all let me see yeah
云，也许这都是让我明白的
okay good so you do you cloud a lot off
好吧，好吗？
login and that will redirect you to a
登录，这会将您重定向到
login screen here I'm going to log in to
登录屏幕在这里，我要登录
my and I'll confirm all the usual things
我和我会确认所有平常的事情
and there we go now I'm back in I'm back
现在我们走了，我回来了，我回来了
to where I was before but I'm logged in
到我以前的位置，但我已经登录
right in that's the you know G cloud it
就在那，你知道G云吗
gave me some information actually it
给了我一些信息
says I can set my config I can my
说我可以设置我的配置
current project is this I can change it
当前项目是这个，我可以更改它
by saying GG cloud config except project
通过说除项目外的GG云配置
ID and then once you've done that
ID，然后一旦完成
actually installs a config file in your
实际上在您的计算机中安装了一个配置文件
home directory that your G cloud API
您的G Cloud API的主目录
will use whenever it talks to Google
与Google通话时将使用
cloud so it's sort of like you've got a
云，这有点像你有一个
working project and all things you do
工作项目和您所做的所有事情
you know in your operating system will
你知道你的操作系统会
work against that project unless you
除非您反对该项目
switch it
切换它
and the same kind of thing is true for
同样的事情也适用
when you use the api's right we're gonna
当您使用api的权利时，我们将
use the G cloud API Google cloud API s
使用G cloud API Google cloud API
and these api is all assume the presence
这些api都假定存在
of this authentication sort of document
认证文件的种类
this a certificate sort of it's not
这不是一个证书
oaken is it's it's a it's a file that
橡树是它是一个文件
has some data in it right um you can
里面有一些数据，你可以
with spring cloud you can actually get
有了春天的云，你实际上可以得到
this stuff you can source it from an
这些东西你可以从一个
environment variable if you want but
环境变量，如果您想
whatever you do you need to make that
无论您需要做什么，
available and then once you've done that
可用，然后一旦完成
you're authenticated so there's not
您已通过身份验证，所以没有
different keys per service or anything
每个服务或其他任何不同的密钥
like that you just have the Google Cloud
就像你只有Google Cloud
configuration for authentication and
认证和配置
you're done all right that makes working
您已经做好了使工作正常的一切
with this pretty easy once you've
有了这个非常简单的
figured it out I should I should caution
想通了我应该警告
and that's a big provision there okay so
那是很大的准备，所以
we've got now Google Cloud we've got
我们现在有了Google Cloud
we've seen you got this nice shell I've
我们已经看到你有这个漂亮的贝壳了
got a bunch of things that I want to do
有很多我想做的事情
today in our little example and we're
今天在我们的小例子中，我们
gonna use some of the services that have
将使用一些具有
been provisioned here let's start with
在这里配置，让我们开始
the plain-jane sort of stuff right we're
简朴的东西，我们
gonna work with a sequel database and
将使用续集数据库和
here you can easily create a number of
在这里您可以轻松创建许多
different types of sequel databases
不同类型的续集数据库
you've got my sequel and post guys okay
你有我的续集并张贴家伙好
I've got my sequel instance here so I'm
我这里有续集实例，所以我
gonna go back to my shell here my portal
要回到我的外壳在这里我的门户
I'll choose sequel and there I can see
我会选择续集，在那里我可以看到
I've got a my sequel database called
我有一个名为的续集数据库
reservations it's in US central one and
保留在美国中部
the reservations database has a public
预订数据库有一个公共的
IP address and a instance connection
IP地址和实例连接
name and the name of the database is
名称和数据库名称是
called reservations so there's that I
叫预订，所以我
can look at the overview for the
可以查看概述
databases and I can see there's the
数据库，我可以看到
database and if I launch the shell right
数据库，如果我启动外壳正确
if I launch the shell here connect using
如果我在这里启动外壳连接使用
cloud shell I can actually get dumped
我实际上可以丢弃的云壳
into my my sequence I'm going to hit
按照我的顺序，我要打
enter g-cloud sequel connect
输入g-cloud续集连接
reservations user root equals whatever
保留用户root等于
and it's gonna punch a hole in the
它会在
platform and let me let me actually work
平台，让我让我实际工作
off there the kid with it
那边的孩子
sequences which i think is really cool I
我认为真的很酷的序列
mean that's just a it's very convenient
就是说这很方便
you can actually get access you can
您实际上可以访问
actually configure the firewall and and
实际配置防火墙，并且
and talk to it from outside if you like
如果愿意，可以从外面和它说话
but it's just really compelling that I
但是我真的很引人注目
can do it from within the portal right
可以从门户网站内部进行操作
that's one of the things that I think
这是我认为的一件事
you'll find is true for for for Google
您会发现适用于Google
Cloud and for Microsoft desorbs that
云计算和Microsoft解散了
working with a portal is very efficient
使用门户网站非常有效
right you can get a lot of stuff done
对，你可以完成很多工作
there so I'm not going to create a brand
在那里，所以我不会建立品牌
new instance of of my sequel because for
我的续集的新实例，因为
reasons I'll never understand this takes
我永远不会理解的原因
minutes it takes several minutes to
分钟需要几分钟
create a brand new instance of postcodes
创建一个全新的邮政编码实例
or my sequel and it's just a single
或我的续集，这只是一个
instance you know it's just a simple
你知道这只是一个简单的例子
note but if I want to use the highly
请注意，但是如果我想使用高度
available highly consistent multi-tenant
可用的高度一致的多租户
caught you know the spanner database
抓到你知道扳手数据库
then that takes no time at all which
那根本就不需要时间
which is kind of weird right it's kind
这是一种很奇怪的权利
of interesting that it you know they'd
有趣的是，你知道他们会
have some trouble with something as
遇到一些麻烦
innocuous as a my sequel database but I
作为我的续集数据库是无害的，但我
guess it's just maybe the way it was
猜猜这也许就是这样
designed isn't multi-tenant I don't know
设计不是多租户，我不知道
we can never know either way
我们永远都不会知道
it's already pre provisioned I'm not
它已经预先配置好了，我不是
gonna do it again I've got this instance
我要再做一次
so let's go ahead and build a new
所以我们继续构建一个新的
applications do that here we're gonna
应用程序将在这里完成
call this application beautiful GC P and
将此应用称为美丽的GC P
I'm gonna use the GCP support or bring
我将使用GCP支持或带来
in TCP messaging the GCP storage we're
在TCP消息传递中的GCP存储
gonna use Baumbach we're gonna use
将使用鲍姆巴赫，我们将使用
actuator when you use JBC we're gonna
执行器，当您使用JBC时，我们将
use my sequel we're gonna use what else
用我的续集，我们要用别的
do we want to well let the web support I
我们是否想让网络支持我
guess we want sleuth and that's it
猜我们想要侦探，仅此而已
that's it that's it I think probably
我想大概就是这样
everything we need
我们需要的一切
I don't know if I even need my sequel we
我不知道我是否需要续集
don't need that right really and that's
真的不需要那个权利，那是
it that's gonna be enough for us to get
足以让我们得到
started
开始了
I think ok let's do it hit go all right
我认为好吧，我们继续吧
so no downloads you want to open this up
所以没有下载您想打开它
and first things first we're gonna build
首先我们要建立
an application that talks to my my
与我的我说话的应用程序
sequel database and so we need a bit of
续集数据库，所以我们需要一些
configuration which we'll start with
我们将开始的配置
here in the property file we're gonna
在属性文件中，我们要
say that one then GCP you know you just
说一个然后GCP，你知道你只是
be database named an instance connection
被数据库命名为实例连接
name so instance connection name and the
名称，因此实例连接名称和
database name
数据库名称
we're right in front us before right so
我们在前面就在我们前面，所以
let's just get that the database name
让我们获取数据库名称
was reservations and the connection name
是预订和连接名称
was here so where did we put it there
在这里，所以我们把它放在哪里
just there which actually just copy and
就在那里，实际上只是复制并
pasted it good thank you
粘贴好谢谢
all right there's my sequel and I'm
好吧，有我的续集，我是
gonna go to our beautiful GCP
要去我们美丽的GCP
application and write some code to write
应用程序并编写一些代码来编写
some data to that database getting data
一些数据到该数据库获取数据
out of it the sequel table so let's look
从续集表中，让我们看一下
at that now that we're in the in the
那时我们在
show here let's look at that we'll say
在这里显示让我们看看我们会说
well first of all I say show tables
首先，我说要显示表格
that's how I showed a basis okay use
这就是我显示基础可以使用的方式
reservations and then there will have
保留，然后会有
the ability to show the tables select
显示表格的能力选择
all from reservations and there we go we
全部来自预订，然后我们去了
got some data in the application and you
在应用程序中有一些数据，您
know an ID column and the name column so
知道ID列和名称列，所以
let's go back to our application we've
让我们回到我们的应用程序中
hit an entity to manage data of that
打实体来管理该实体的数据
type right so data at all our
输入正确的数据
constructor and know where our
构造函数，知道我们在哪里
constructor and here I'm going to just
构造函数，这里我只是
create a long ID and a string name field
创建一个长ID和一个字符串名称字段
okay so private string name and that's
好的，所以私有字符串名称就是
the essence if I want to express of
如果我想表达的本质
course that's it that's my simple little
当然就是我简单的一点
detail and we'll create a demo here
详细信息，我们将在此处创建一个演示
class my sequel demo and there just be a
我的续集演示课上，只有一个
beam that will get invoked when the
当
application starts up like so public
应用程序像公共一样启动
demo inception and it'll be a rebel
演示开始，它将是反叛者
spring green spring component brother
春天绿色春天组成兄弟
and all we're going to do is when we use
而我们要做的就是当我们使用
the spring form of JDBC template okay
JDBC模板的春季形式还可以
the venerable tried into JDBC template
尝试过的JDBC模板
them so there's that
他们，所以有
okay I'm gonna say steam docked bum you
好吧，我要说蒸汽停靠你
know ray that's what we want to query
知道射线就是我们要查询的东西
the data that'll be even easier so let's
数据将变得更加容易，让我们
just say JDBC template dot query select
只是说JDBC模板点查询选择
all from reservation new role mapper
全部来自预订新角色映射器
okay there's a reservation and there we
好的，有预订，我们在那里
go there's our detail that we're going
去，有我们要去的细节
to turn these out real mapper say yeah
把这些变成真实的映射器说是的
RS - get long ID autostop get string
RS-获取长ID自动停止获取字符串
name already replace that with a lambda
名称已经用lambda替换了
and there we go okay and now I want to
然后我们可以了，现在我想
do some just visit each one of those
做一些只是访问那些
I'll just log it out and enter it to log
我将其注销并输入以进行登录
it I'll use a logger from Lombok so say
我将使用龙目岛的记录仪
log4j - and well then visit each one
log4j-然后访问每个
that comes back for each log info okay
每个日志信息都可以返回
run this let's see what we get
运行这个让我们看看我们得到了什么
now it's going to start but in the
现在它将开始，但是在
meantime you know what I think I like
同时你知道我想我喜欢什么
this inside the class so it's scoped
这在类中，所以它的范围
private static abre
私人静电
so let's see um it wants me to configure
所以让我们来看看UM是否要我配置
a URL
网址
do I have to I think I did everything I
我是否必须做我所做的一切
need
需要
oh I need to actually add them I see
哦，我需要实际添加它们
full starter that makes sense okay
完全可以的入门者，还可以
so it's telling me right there in there
所以告诉我在那里
what it wants and I'm sitting there just
它想要什么，我正坐在那里
under staring at it when Dan went once
当丹走一次时盯着它
so spring cloud GCP will start a sequel
所以春天的云GCP会开始续集
my sequel we give to that maybe our and
我的续集，我们可能就是
now we can restart the application
现在我们可以重新启动应用程序
already it goes up open away and what is
它已经打开了，什么是
the issue now
现在的问题
reservations to my query reservations
保留到我的查询保留
and you know I just realized something
而且你知道我刚意识到
here I've got a connection pool that I
在这里，我有一个连接池
should probably care about and I can do
应该大概在乎，我可以做
that in the same sort of way I would do
用我会做的同样的方式
any other connection pool I can actually
我实际上可以连接的任何其他连接池
configure for example pick car this is
配置例如接车，这是
actually a thing today
今天实际上是一件事情
just a regular sequel connection that is
只是一个常规的续集连接
gonna be configured for us first by
首先要为我们配置
google cloud and spring cloud innovation
Google Cloud和Spring Cloud创新
for google cloud but then it's just a
对于谷歌云，但那只是一个
data source that we can actually
我们可以实际使用的数据源
configure like anything else
像其他任何东西一样配置
okay look at that there's our data
好的，看看我们的数据
starts up Violetta charge myself I'm
启动Violetta我自己充电
Marcin Olga doctor sigh ray right sang
Marcin Olga医生叹息右唱
my friend at Google so we've got now
我在Google的朋友，所以我们现在
just data right very easy to do now of
只是数据现在非常容易做到
course you might be wondering you know I
当然你可能想知道你知道我
can spit up on my sequence into anywhere
可以把我的序列吐到任何地方
and if you know me you know I'm a big
如果你认识我，你知道我很大
fan of using the differentiating
使用差异化的粉丝
services that are available on each of
每个服务都可用
these platforms you know be as portable
您知道这些平台可移植
as possible otherwise you know use Cloud
否则，您知道使用云
Foundry use kubernetes for your apps for
代工厂将kubernetes用于您的应用
a regular line of business apps for
常规业务应用程序
regular apps and indeed there's no
常规应用，确实​​没有
reason to tie yourself to a platform
将自己绑定到平台的原因
when you can do that now technically
当您现在可以从技术上做到这一点时
easier you know less cost alternative
更容易了解，成本更低
but if you are on the path then should
但是如果你在路上，那应该
absolutely if you need to exploit the
绝对如果您需要利用
things that are compelling about that
令人信服的事情
platform take full advantage of it so my
平台充分利用了它，所以我的
sequel is interesting but I can run my
续集很有趣，但我可以运行
sequel in any of a number of different
多种不同的续集
ways and I can even do so in a
种方式，我什至可以做到
high-level way this isn't necessarily
高层次的方式，这不一定
the best way to run my sequel that's
运行我的续集的最好方法是
ever been created
曾经被创造
instead when I go to Google Cloud one of
而是当我去Google Cloud时，
the things I want to take advantage of
我想利用的东西
his banner now spanner is a a a
现在他的旗帜是aaa
so-called no sequel datastore that was
所谓的没有续集数据存储
developed and kind of quietly announced
发达，并悄悄宣布
in 2012 in announcing some other thing
在2012年宣布了其他事情
by Google spanner is being used inside
由Google扳手内部使用
of Google for a lot of different
Google的不同
projects and it was born I think to read
项目，它诞生了，我想阅读
sort of a literature on it was born as
关于它的某种文学诞生于
they sort of result or as a sort of
他们是某种结果或某种
reaction to what they had sort of
对他们有什么反应
discovered anecdotally in within Google
在Google内被发现
which is that a lot of large websites a
这是很多大型网站
lot of different projects within Google
Google中的许多不同项目
needed scale they needed the sort of big
需要规模，他们需要那种大
tables like scale that they hadn't
像秤这样的桌子，他们没有
gotten before in in Google but they
曾经在Google遇到过，但他们
didn't want to have to reinvent
不想重塑
primitives to support consistency things
支持一致性事物的原语
like transactions right they didn't when
喜欢交易，他们没有
I have to reinvent all these primitives
我必须重塑所有这些原始元素
to get that but they did want the high
得到那个，但他们确实想要高
availability they didn't want the scale
可用性，他们不想要规模
so they had something called mega store
所以他们有一个叫做大型商店的东西
mega store while it served a lot of the
大型商店，虽然它服务了很多
use cases that people had within Google
人们在Google中使用的用例
for for their double use cases it didn't
对于他们的双重用例，它没有
offer nearly the same level of scale but
提供几乎相同的规模，但
that's ok it was good
没关系，这很好
enough even for Google and so people
即使对于Google来说也足够
chose that seemingly inferior technology
选择了看似劣质的技术
because it allowed developers to get you
因为它使开发人员可以帮助您
know interesting work done as opposed to
知道有趣的工作而不是
spending all this time reinventing all
花所有的时间重塑所有
these basic feminists on top of BigTable
BigTable上的这些基本女权主义者
and so as a result of that I guess they
因此，我想他们
eventually decided well we need to you
最终决定好，我们需要你
know it'd be nice to have something that
知道有一些东西会很好
provides all these things so spanner is
提供所有这些东西，所以扳手是
a globally available consistent and
全球可用的一致和
distributed replicated datastore now you
分布式复制数据存储现在您
know to hear me just say that didn't I
知道听到我只是说不是
just didn't I just say didn't just
我只是说不只是
didn't you just say Josh that that's a
你不是只是说乔希那是一个
database that solves consistency
解决一致性的数据库
availability and partition ability are
可用性和分区能力是
you sure you understand what you're
你确定你了解自己
saying
说
and yeah I kind of scratched my head at
是的，我有点挠头
that at first as well it does seem to be
起初似乎也确实是
a bit of a quandary how does it solve
有点困惑如何解决
the cat problem and the answer is that
猫的问题，答案是
it doesn't right it doesn't really solve
这是不对的，并不能真正解决
the cap problem it doesn't actually
上限问题实际上并没有
somehow get all three out of three what
不知何故三分之三
it does do is that it takes advantage of
它的确是利用了
incredible you know space-age sort of
不可思议，你知道太空时代
data sense of technology that Google
Google的数据技术意识
have and incredible connectivity between
之间有着不可思议的连通性
data centers you know fiber connectivity
您知道光纤连接的数据中心
between data centers and it uses a log
在数据中心之间，它使用日志
that reconciles things based on time
根据时间调和事物
steps and those time stamps time stamps
步骤和那些时间戳记
are incredibly accurate they're based on
是非常准确的，它们基于
atomic clocks and GPS time and GPS you
原子钟，GPS时间和GPS您
know signals and I mean all sorts of
知道信号，我的意思是各种各样的
interesting stuff that you just you
有趣的东西，你就是你
wouldn't have in a stock commodity data
不会有库存商品数据
center these things are what allow
集中这些东西是允许的
Google to sort of cheat they kind of
Google有点作弊
fudge you know it gets all three of
忽悠你知道它得到了全部三个
those things because it's fast enough
这些东西，因为它足够快
that it effectively gets through all
它有效地贯穿了所有人
those three of those things right but
那三件事对了
it's not actually solving the problem
并没有真正解决问题
but the point is it's good enough it
但关键是它足够好
feels like it does right um and this is
感觉像是对的，这是
just one of those things where just
这些只是其中之一
straight up I we're not gonna have the
直线上升，我不会有
ability to run a spanner even in our
即使在我们的团队中也可以运行扳手
data center even if we had the software
数据中心，即使我们拥有软件
even if Google gave us the software
即使Google给了我们软件
you're not going to get the same effect
你不会得到相同的效果
this is one of those things where you
这是你其中的一件事
should just let Google do it they're
应该让Google去做
good at it they've got the
擅长他们有
infrastructure they can run this at the
基础设施，他们可以在
level that we they need to run it to be
他们需要运行它的水​​平
able to make it worth it using and
能够使用和使其值得
that's just one of those sort of
那只是其中一种
innovations that you get by by building
通过建设获得的创新
on that platform so let's do that let's
在那个平台上，让我们做到这一点，让我们
use banner here and we're going to use
在这里使用横幅，我们将使用
the spring cloud GCP starter spanner
Spring Cloud GCP入门扳手
maybe the spring started data spinner
也许春天开始了数据微调器
okay so either way we'll say okay and
好的，无论哪种方式，我们都会说好的，
this but we do want data spanner
这个，但是我们确实想要数据扳手
okay okay there's my spanner it depends
好吧好吧，这取决于我的扳手
you know let's look at spanner here okay
你知道让我们看一下扳手好吗
I've got spanner in my portal just as
我的门户中也有扳手
before you go here you can see it says
在你去这里之前，你可以看到它说
well it says spanner and when you go to
好吧，它说扳手，当你去
spanner you can see there's a spanner
扳手，你会看到有一个扳手
database called reservations demo and
数据库，名为reservation demo和
when I go there I can click on
当我去那里我可以点击
reservations and when I go here it says
保留，当我去这里时说
reservations click on that and it shows
预订单击，它显示
me that I've got a table you know with
我有一张你知道的桌子
an ID and a name I can look at the DDL
我可以看一下DDL的ID和名称
and there's even a sequel like language
甚至还有续集之类的语言
that you can use this is very similar to
您可以使用此功能非常类似于
sequel and this is ID and name right
续集，这是ID和名称正确
it's a pretty simple right pretty simple
这很简单，很简单
you can actually query it as well
您实际上也可以查询它
there's it supports sequel queries so I
它支持续集查询，所以我
can say select all from reservations run
可以说从预订运行中全选
the query I get these records back right
查询我得到这些记录正确
so that's cool but it doesn't support
所以很酷，但不支持
sequel queries for rent for rights for
续集租金的权利查询
items only for weeds but usually that's
仅用于杂草的物品，但通常是
enough right that's usually enough so we
足够的权利通常就足够了，所以我们
can actually copy and paste all that and
实际上可以复制并粘贴所有
then delete this reservations
然后删除此预订
okay and delete all this one
好，删除所有这一个
no no I delete okay so
不，不，我删除，好吧
click on this again we can create a
再点击一次，我们可以创建一个
table and it has text paste it create
表并粘贴创建的文本
back where we started okay so there we
回到我们开始的地方，所以在那里
go there's our data we're going to
去有我们要去的数据
create it and now we can actually talk
创建它，现在我们可以实际交谈了
to it from our application in order to
从我们的应用程序中
talk to it from application of course we
从我们的应用程序谈起
need some configuration just like before
像以前一样需要一些配置
so we'll go back to our property file
所以我们回到属性文件
spanner and we're going to use spanner
扳手，我们将使用扳手
whoops
哎呀
spanner instance ID and to get the
扳手实例ID并获取
instance ID we can go here and the
实例ID，我们可以去这里
instance ID is the reservations demo
实例ID是预订演示
that's this up here so reservations demo
就在这里，所以预订演示
and then finally we need the database so
最后我们需要数据库
spanner database equals reservations
扳手数据库等于保留量
alright good so there's our our
好吧，所以我们有
configuration for spanner and now with
扳手的配置，现在
that and done we can create a document
这样就可以创建一个文档
to manage our data in using spring data
使用spring数据来管理我们的数据
and so here give it a field called ID
所以在这里给它一个叫ID的字段
field called name and this is going to
名为名称的字段，这将
be a string and the reason is because
是一个字符串，原因是
we're using the highly distributed
我们正在使用高度分散的
highly available data stored so
高可用性数据存储，因此
monotonically incrementing integers or
单调递增整数或
numbers along these kinds of things they
他们沿着这些东西编号
don't really work well in this kind of
在这种情况下真的不能很好地工作
environment so we need to provide a
环境，所以我们需要提供一个
unique ID and we're going to do so using
唯一ID，我们将使用
a UUID which is a string so this will be
一个UUID，它是一个字符串，因此它将是
a thing that we're going to map to a
我们要映射到一个东西
table there's a name it's gonna called
桌子上有个名字叫
reservations like so use that data at
像这样的预订使用
all arcs constructor at Nords
Nords的所有弧线构造函数
constructor and then we're gonna create
构造函数，然后我们将创建
a repository as always to persist
一如既往的存储库
instances of this data to the database
此数据的实例到数据库
ok so we're gonna use a spanner
好，我们要用扳手
repository
资料库
except reservation is there we go okay
除了预订，我们还可以
are my keys of type string and now I
是我的字符串类型的键，现在我
want to save some data to the database
想要将一些数据保存到数据库
so spanner demo that you can listen up
这样的扳手演示，您可以收听
application ready done event public void
应用程序就绪事件公共无效
and data I'm sorry this will be a
和数据我很抱歉这将是一个
component and what I'm going to do we're
组件以及我要做的事情
gonna write to dance so we're going to
要写跳舞，所以我们要
need to inject our spanner repository
需要注入我们的扳手库
here and a definite constructor and
这里有一个确定的构造函数，
first things first I want to delete some
首先，我想删除一些
data so this that delete all and then
数据，这样就删除所有然后
finally when we write write to the data
最后，当我们写数据时
so we'll say stream that of Ray okay so
所以我们说流雷很好，所以
there's a few people and what I'm gonna
有几个人，我要
do is I'm going to map each one to a new
我要做的是将每个映射到一个新的
reservation no name and that each one of
保留没有名字，并且每个
those she would record in the database
她将记录在数据库中的那些
right all right and I just want to visit
好吧，我只想参观
each one that I've done and I'm going to
我所做的每一件事，我都会去
just confirm it by using a logger
只需使用记录器进行确认
so I'll say at log4j to okay
所以我会说在log4j可以
log : info yeah but okay and
日志：信息是的，但是还可以
[Music]
[音乐]
we're going to start
我们要开始
there's a my sequel whoops what just
我的续集大叫什么
happened
发生了
ID must button B not know aha so what I
ID必须是按钮B不知道啊哈我
did wrong is I forgot to provide a UUID
做错了是我忘了提供UUID
which I even picked up what happened and
我什至拿起发生了什么事，
I forgot to act on yeah so we started it
我忘了采取行动，所以我们开始了
was a silly unforced error I'm sorry
很抱歉，这是一个愚蠢的错误
about that
关于那个
okay there's my seagull stuff and there
好，那里有我的海鸥东西
is no span or data right and we can
没有跨度或数据权，我们可以
actually confirm as much by going here
实际上通过去这里确认
and doing the query run the query there
并执行查询在那里运行查询
it is
它是
date murderer Violetta mark Olga hey
约会杀人犯维奥莱塔（Voletta）马克·奥尔加（嘿）
Andy draconian etc okay so there we go
Andy draconian等，好的，我们去了
not bad how we got some data in the
不错，我们如何从中获取一些数据
database now that's just data I wouldn't
现在数据库只是我不会的数据
mind us I want to store some data as
介意我们我想将一些数据存储为
well and so you know what can we do here
好，所以你知道我们可以在这里做什么
well I suppose we could use a restore
好吧，我想我们可以使用还原
image data like binary data right and so
像二进制数据这样的图像数据等等
one way to do this is to use the storage
一种方法是使用存储
service there in um in Google cloud and
在Google Cloud中提供服务
so I think we should do that what you do
所以我认为我们应该按照您的意愿去做
we can store data we've already got this
我们可以存储已经拥有的数据
storage service here right and we can
存储服务在这里，我们可以
store it
储存它
under let's see proud
在下面让我们看到骄傲
this one I think
我认为这个
we've got the cat image there okay so we
我们那里有猫的形象，所以我们
can use this later on we can actually
可以稍后再使用
refer to this from our Java code fairly
从我们的Java代码中公平地引用
easily in using the resource abstraction
轻松使用资源抽象
and one of the reasons that we might be
这也是我们可能成为的原因之一
able to want to use this is to take
能够使用这个是要
advantage of some of the other services
其他一些服务的优势
that are in Google cloud one of the
在Google云中
other services that's in Google cloud is
Google云中的其他服务是
the Google vision API well the vision
Google视觉API很好
API is really smart you can give it an
API真的很聪明，您可以给它一个
image and we'll identify certain facts
图片，我们将确定某些事实
about that image so we have this cat
关于那个图像，所以我们有这只猫
picture that's managed that I've already
我已经管理过的图片
uploaded here's the cat picture it's a
这里上传的是猫的照片
cat and we can use the Google vision API
猫，我们可以使用Google视觉API
to pull this data down using the storage
使用存储拉下这些数据
API so we can actually create a vision
API，因此我们实际上可以创建一个愿景
demo okay destroy this here that
演示好吧，在这里销毁这个
component and let's say at event
组件，让我们在活动中说
listener application ready event public
侦听器应用程序就绪事件公共
void demo okay and here there is no
无效的演示好了，这里没有
pre-configured auto configured sort of
预配置的自动配置的
API for vision we have to actually do
我们必须做的视觉API
this work ourselves but that's okay
这项工作我们自己做，但是没关系
because this is one of those things
因为这是其中之一
where by virtue of the fact that we're
鉴于我们
using spring cloud and the GCP
使用Spring Cloud和GCP
integration for spring cloud the
整合Spring Cloud
authentication is the authentication
认证就是认证
auto-configuration already results in us
自动配置已经导致我们
getting a credentials object that we can
得到一个我们可以的凭证对象
then use to authenticate to other Google
然后用于向其他Google进行身份验证
Cloud api's even if those APIs don't
即使这些API没有提供Cloud API，
themselves have integrations in Auto
本身与Auto集成
configuration in in spinning cloud gzq
在旋转云gzq中进行配置
project so what we're gonna do is we're
项目，所以我们要做的是
going to first define a beam of type
首先要定义一个类型的梁
image annotator
图像注释器
client actually what I need is I need
客户我真正需要的是我需要的
the vision API first so vision I think
首先是视觉API，所以我认为
that's it all right
没关系
I want to believe that's right you know
我想相信那是对的
what I'm gonna go with it let's just
我要去做的就是
leave it or leave it in it'll
留在里面或留在里面
it's probably fine it's probably fine so
可能很好，所以可能很好
we don't create a beam type image and
我们不会创建光束类型的图像，
Cato client and then inject the
Cato客户程序，然后注入
credential provider make sure you get
凭证提供者确保您得到
the right one there and we're gonna say
合适的那个，我们要说
return image and Cato client using that
返回图像和Cato客户端使用该图像
and use duck-billed no you Janet a toe
并用鸭嘴不给你珍妮脚趾
client dot create when I come back to
客户点创建，当我回到
this
这个
yeah that should be it so we need that
是的，应该这样，所以我们需要
and we're gonna say that this needs a
我们要说这需要一个
image annotator settings and annotator
图像注释器设置和注释器
settings Doc's noob builder die set
设置Doc的noob生成器模具集
credential provider CP doc the old okay
凭证提供者CP doc旧的还可以
and look an exception if we need to
并在需要时查找例外
shake off any red squigglies build
摆脱任何红色的曲线
alright here we go so there's my image
好了，我们走了，所以有我的形象
annotated plan and I'm getting this
带注释的计划，我正在得到这个
credentials provider from the spring
从春季开始的凭证提供者
cloud integration now this image
云集成现在此图像
annotator client is fairly hey it's
注释者客户端相当嘿
stateful it's heavy I actually for some
有状态的，我实际上有些沉重
reason I contract the bed as hey for its
我之所以把床缩了一下
stay for and heavy which is yes I agree
留下来，沉重，是的，我同意
a little heavy and a little hateful but
有点沉重和可恨
um we had this image annotator client it
嗯，我们有这个图像注释器客户端
is stateful and heavy it's not one of
有状态又沉重，不是其中之一
those things you want to keep around
你想保留的那些东西
forever
永远
you should definitely let this spring
你绝对应该让这个春天
application context do the right thing
应用程序上下文做正确的事
and help dispose of it you'll notice
并帮助您处理它
that it implements Auto closeable when
它实现了自动关闭
spring sees that are being influenced
春天看到正在受到影响
this interface
这个介面
it'll automatically destroy it or
它会自动销毁它，或者
dispose of it right it'll it'll call
正确处理它会叫
clothes when the application is done
完成申请后的衣服
this is great for for example with for
这很棒，例如
for you know try with resources that
因为你知道尝试资源
kind of thing and in spring ignite you
那种东西，在春天点燃你
know it understands that in the same way
知道它以相同的方式理解
that it understands pre destroyed right
它了解预毁权
or disposable beam so we're gonna use
或一次性光束，我们将使用
that when they also use a mute annotate
当他们还使用静音注释时
or claim private image annotator client
或声明私有图像注释者客户端
you add that to this and what we just
您将其添加到此以及我们只是
want to inject in our in our vision demo
希望在我们的视觉演示中注入我们
we're gonna inject the resource from the
我们将从
application from the cloud right from
来自云端的应用程序
spring power so I'm gonna say that we
春天的力量，所以我要说我们
want to talk to GS you know
想跟你知道的GS说话
same bucket cap jpg there's the cat
同样的斗帽jpg那只猫
there's that all right so we're actually
没关系，所以我们实际上
injecting the cat and we got the image
注入猫，我们得到了图像
annotated client and what we're going to
带注释的客户以及我们要做什么
do here is we're going to use the image
这里要做的是我们将要使用图像
annotator api but first we need the
注释器api，但首先我们需要
bytes of the cat okay equals file copy
猫的字节数等于文件副本
utils dot copy bytes to array the cat
utils点复制字节来排列猫
get input stream and I'm sorry
得到输入流，对不起
this time we sort stuck it input stream
这次我们对输入流进行了分类
all right so there's my bytes and what I
好吧，这是我的字节，还有我的
want to do is honor work with it then
想做的就是与之合作
byte array so I'm going to use a bat
字节数组，所以我要使用蝙蝠
annotate image response response equals
注释图像响应响应等于
this stock image annotated client dot
这个库存图像注释的客户点
back annotate images and then we made a
返回注释图像，然后我们做了一个
request this requires a collection of
要求这需要收集
requests so let's see
请求，让我们看看
it's gonna be an annotate image request
这将是一个带注释的图像请求
dot new builder add a feature and what
点新的构建器添加功能以及什么
we're trying to do is when to describe
我们试图做的是何时描述
what things we want to recognize in the
我们想在哪些事情上认识
in the image right not that type naval
在图像中，不是那种海军
detection
检测
and you want this to be the data that's
而您希望这是
coming from the bytes here so image that
来自这里的字节，所以图像
new builder done set content and I
新的构建者完成了设置内容，而我
create a byte string out of its dot to
从其点创建一个字节字符串以
copy from
复制自
right yeah cat right okay good good good
对，对，对，对，对，好，好，好
so what do we got way we're gonna we
所以我们该怎么办
have here let's see let's store all that
在这里，让我们看看让我们存储所有
there's the image data I just wanna
有我只想要的图像数据
build yeah build okay the old when I say
建立是的，建立好旧的当我说
build okay I wouldn't get collection of
建立好吧，我不会收集
these told me so collections dot
这些告诉我，所以收藏点
singleton this build there we go
单身人士，我们去那里建立
where's that give us that gives us a
那在哪里给我们，给我们一个
response and what I'm gonna do is just
回应，我要做的就是
log out the results there so I'll say
在那里注销结果，所以我会说
log that info of course we don't have
记录我们当然没有的信息
the logger so that's just didn't check
记录器，所以只是没有检查
that here up-to-date - okay the info log
这是最新的-好的信息日志
out the results hey okay so there's our
结果出来，好吧，所以我们
data
数据
these today okay
今天好吗
okay good stuff now let's see let's run
好东西，现在让我们来看看吧
this and see what we get on the remand
看看我们得到的还款
look at that it has recognized that this
看它已经意识到
is a Scottish this is a cat with a with
是苏格兰人，这是与
it it has said that this is a British
它说这是英国人
semi long hair with 75 percent
半长发，百分之七十五
probability this is a this is a picture
这是一张图片的概率
that hasn't cat it has a snout a nose it
那不是猫，鼻子是鼻子
has grass in the background that's fauna
在动物群的背景中有草
it's a cat-like mammal certainly is it's
这是像猫一样的哺乳动物，肯定是
a small to medium sized cat although I
一只中小型猫，虽然我
don't know if I would I don't know if I
我不知道我是否会
agree with that I think that's a pretty
同意，我认为这是一个漂亮的
fed perfect time we've got a mammal yes
喂饱了完美的时光，我们有了哺乳动物
check whiskers darn tootin we've got a
检查胡须，也有一个
cat right good stuff so it seems to have
猫对的好东西，所以似乎有
a 99% confidence that this is a cat
对这只猫有99％的信心
which you know fair that's fair we don't
你知道那公平吗我们不公平
you know missing legs like I'm pretty
你知道我的腿很像我很漂亮
I'm pretty impressed with how confident
我对自己的自信印象深刻
is given that it doesn't have like limbs
被赋予它没有四肢
it's just a flying fluff ball so that's
这只是一个飞毛绒球，所以
pretty impressive Google good stuff
Google令人印象深刻的好东西
really impressive now we have save some
真令人印象深刻，现在我们已经节省了一些
data we use the resource abstraction
我们使用资源抽象的数据
here to pull down data from the Google
在这里从Google提取数据
cloud storage service right where you
云存储服务就在您哪里
have to do anything special there to get
必须做一些特别的事情才能得到
that to work and that's cool I like that
工作，那很酷，我喜欢
you know there's a bunch of other things
你知道还有很多其他的事情
we could do I guess we could I guess the
我们可以做到，我可以猜到
next thing we could look at is a
接下来我们要看的是
messaging intubation let's do that one
信息插管，让我们做到这一点
right so you know it's very easy to
对，所以您知道这很容易
connect services or with Google cloud
连接服务或与Google Cloud
because that Google cloud pub/sub so we
因为那个Google云端发布/订阅所以我们
can actually take advantage of this as
实际上可以利用这一点
long as we add the right dependency so
只要我们添加正确的依赖关系
we need the Google cloud the spring
春天我们需要谷歌云
cloud used to be started pumped up right
云曾经被启动了
so spring GCP starter pops up all right
所以春季GCP入门者会弹出
goodbye and we're gonna need some
再见，我们需要一些
property configuration and we don't have
属性配置，我们没有
anything that we need to do here for
我们在这里需要做的任何事情
that so we're good and now let's just go
这样我们就很好了，现在让我们开始吧
ahead and build an application pub/sub
提前建立一个应用程序发布/订阅
demo event listener
演示事件监听器
application ready event class public
应用就绪事件类公共
void demo throws exception and river
无效的演示引发异常和河
spring beam with eight pub sub
带有八个酒吧子的弹簧梁
subscription up sub publisher template
订阅子发布者模板
publisher private final pub sub
出版商私人最终发布子
subscribe a template subscribe butter
订阅模板订阅黄油
alright inject those into the
好吧，将它们注入
constructor
建设者
l wanna and when it register first a
我想当它第一次注册时
subscriber and what we're gonna just
订户，我们将要
want to use the pre provisioned
想要使用预先设置的
subscription and topic that we've got
订阅和主题
here in Google Cloud so let's see what
在Google Cloud中，让我们看看
we got here where's my where's my pub
我们到了这里，我的酒吧在哪里
sub okay
子还好
search you know it's one of those things
搜索您知道这是其中之一
that grew with us quite well search so
与我们一起成长很好的搜索，所以
let's just do that and when I go to the
让我们来做，当我去
pub sub section I'm see that there's
pub子部分，我看到
three really three different um you know
三个真的三个不同的你知道
pieces of interest or things of interest
感兴趣的事物
there's the topics right let's go back
有正确的主题，让我们回去
here actually
实际上在这里
[Applause]
[掌声]
pub/sub there you go no go back here
pub / sub那里，你走不回这里
there pub/sub see top set topics I guess
那里的酒吧/预订看到了我猜的热门话题
it's a GM topics and then you can create
这是GM主题，然后您可以创建
a topic like so very simple just give it
这么简单的话题就给它
a name I've got one called reservations
我有一个名字叫保留
click on this and then you have a
点击这个，然后你有一个
subscription that lives on the other
另一个订阅
side of it and the subscription is a
它的侧面，订阅是
thing to which consumers connect once
消费者连接一次的事物
you have a topic to which you send
您有一个要发送的主题
messages and a subscription from which
消息和订阅
you consume messages and if you want to
您使用邮件，如果您想
do you know in detail each client has
您是否了解每个客户的详细信息
its own scheme then you can have two
它自己的方案，那么你可以有两个
different subscription if you want them
如果需要，可以使用其他订阅
all to drain the same queue then you can
全部耗尽同一个队列，那么您可以
then you can all just all all the
那你就可以全部
clients can talk to the same
客户可以同一个谈话
subscription I mean you can do all sorts
订阅我的意思是你可以做各种事情
of interesting patterns based on their
基于他们有趣的模式
use of subscriptions here right so I've
在这里使用订阅，所以我已经
got one topic on one subscription this
一个订阅有一个主题
is the topic called reservations sorry
是叫保留对不起的话题
it's Todd's reservation subscription and
这是Todd的预订订阅，
it's going to be a new consumer which is
这将是一个新的消费者
a lambda and we have to explicitly
一个lambda，我们必须明确地
acknowledge the message message okay so
确认消息，好吧
we say message dark AK great and we can
我们说消息黑AK很棒，我们可以
log the message and what I'm gonna do is
记录消息，我要做的是
I'm gonna take the message get the pub
我要带消息去酒吧
sub message get the data and turn the
子消息获取数据并打开
data into a string like so
数据变成这样的字符串
okay I'm gonna log that out maybe that's
好吧，我要注销，也许那是
longer as usual message string utf-8
像通常的消息字符串utf-8一样长
alright good stuff so there we are we're
好东西，所以我们就在这里
just logging the receipt of a message
只是记录消息的接收
this of course lends itself nicely to a
这当然很适合
lambda very cool
lambda很酷
much cleaner so we're subscribing to a
更清洁，所以我们正在订阅
message now let's actually send the
现在，让我们实际发送
message so this time gonna say publisher
消息，所以这次要说发布者
dot publish and we're gonna send this to
点发布，我们将发送给
the subscriptions topic and the message
订阅主题和消息
will just be a string instant dot now to
现在只是一个字符串即时点
string everyone okay so I'm gonna send
串好每个人，所以我要发送
the message get this subscriber and
消息得到这个订户和
that's it that's that's the basis of a
就是这样，这就是
demo it's a very simple demo obviously
演示这显然是一个非常简单的演示
you know real distributed system you'd
你知道真正的分布式系统
have one sending messages to the other
有一个向另一个发送消息
but here I'm just choosing to
但在这里我只是选择
demonstrate the content within the same
展示同一内容
JVM process which I think works just
我认为可以正常工作的JVM进程
fine but it's a little atypical fair
很好，但是有点不典型
enough
足够
resource equals subscriptions publisher
资源等于订阅发布者
reservations huh let me just copy and
保留，让我复制并
paste at that we've been better off by
贴上，我们的状况更好
copying and pasting who knew
复制和粘贴谁知道
okay
好的
message hello we got the message and
消息你好，我们收到消息，
there there it is okay
那里还可以
now you know we've got a application
现在您知道我们有一个应用程序
that talks to two different data storage
谈到两个不同的数据存储
were able to upload images and we were
能够上传图片，我们
able to read images were able to do
能够读取图像，能够做到
image analysis were able to do
图像分析能够做到
intubation and messaging I mean we can
插管和消息传递，我的意思是我们可以
do all sorts of interesting things with
做各种各样有趣的事情
Google cloud and you can see it's fairly
谷歌云，你可以看到它相当
trivial to throw these things together I
琐碎的把这些东西放在一起
would say normally at this point that
在这一点上通常会说
we're ready to go we're ready for
我们准备出发了
production man but um you know that's
制作人，但是你知道那是
not always true is it first of all you
并非总是如此吗？
know being cold complete is not the same
知道冷完是不一样的
as being production worthy we certainly
作为值得生产的我们当然
have not cared for observability and so
不在乎可观察性等等
one thing I like to do is to get you
我想做的一件事就是让你
know all eyes on the behavior of this
所有人都知道这种行为
application and one way to do that is to
应用程序，做到这一点的一种方法是
support the stack driver sort of suite
支持堆栈驱动程序排序套件
of observability tools that Google cloud
谷歌云的可观察性工具
provides so if you go down here there's
提供，所以，如果你下去这里有
a whole bunch of nice tools here that we
一堆很好的工具，我们
can look at so let's do that let's
可以看看，让我们做到这一点，让我们
actually bring in two different
实际上带来了两种不同
dependencies here one is spring cloud
这里的依赖是春天云
just be starter trace okay oh it's
只是入门，好吧，哦，
pretty loud
很大声
all right and the other one is
好吧，另一个是
springtime GCP started logging all right
春季GCP开始记录一切正常
so what those are gonna do is they're
所以这些人要做的是
gonna automatically send information for
将自动发送信息
me to the distributed tracing platform
我到分布式跟踪平台
now what I want to do is I want to trace
现在我要做的是追踪
information in the application and
申请中的信息和
normally you know normally what I would
通常你知道我会怎么做
do in this case is I've set up a spring
在这种情况下，我要做的是弹簧
cloud sleeve and the Zipkin zip kind of
云套和Zipkin拉链
courses a distributed tracing pattern as
将分布式跟踪模式作为
our platform from Twitter that we are
我们来自Twitter的平台
privileged enough to have the
足够有特权
opportunity to contribute to we already
有机会为我们做贡献
sponsored some of its developments right
赞助了它的一些开发权
and so can we use if you've amused it
如果您觉得有趣，我们也可以使用
you know that it's it's a generic
你知道那是通用的
abstraction for which Zipkin is a
Zipkin是一个抽象
compelling implementation Zipkin was
令人信服的实施Zipkin是
inspired by the Google dapper paper
灵感来自Google精巧的论文
right so Google staffer papers but
是的，所以Google员工论文
actually said Zipkin in motion and we
实际上在运动中说Zipkin，我们
can take advantage of that the same
可以利用相同的优势
learning is that led to the sort of
学习是导致那种
evolution of dapper have also taken
小巧的进化
place as you can imagine at Google you
您可以想象的地方在Google
know almost eight nine ten years on and
知道将近八九十年
so what we're gonna use it here is the
所以我们要在这里使用它的是
successor to that ok stackdriver trace
ok堆栈驱动程序跟踪的后继者
so one thing you need to do with the
所以你需要做的一件事
samp but smooth when you use it is to
采样，但使用时要平滑
configure what percentage of the
配置百分之几
requests you want to trace so what I'm
要求您要跟踪，所以我是
gonna do is I'm going to build a simple
我要做的是建立一个简单的
little endpoint again pretty simple I'm
小终点再次很简单我
going to build an endpoint that calls
将要建立一个调用
itself just to drive some traffic so
本身只是为了吸引一些流量
let's create a simple greetings recipe
让我们创建一个简单的问候食谱
for okay and this will just be a rest
好吧，这只是休息
controller that we're going to
我们要去的控制器
instrument it's gonna be using a rest
仪器，它将要使用休息
template that is gonna be instrumented
将要检测的模板
by spring cloud salute so we'll go here
到春天云朵敬礼，所以我们去这里
at bean list template return
在bean列表模板返回
template so okay so there's my rest of
模板好，所以我剩下的
it and spring cloud sleuth will
它和春天的云侦探会
automatically configure an interceptor
自动配置拦截器
that perpetuates trace information now
现在永久保留跟踪信息
in in the sleuth parlance in the open
在公开的侦探中
tracing parlance you've got a trace
追踪说法，您已经追踪
which is the agate journey from A to Z
这是从A到Z的玛瑙之旅
and you have each individual hop along
而且你每个人都有
the way from one node to another from
从一个节点到另一个节点的方式
one logical component boundary to
一个逻辑组件边界
another
另一个
that's a call that's called a span so
这是一个称为跨度的电话
I've got a rest template and I'm gonna
我有一个休息模板，我要
configure it to perpetuate trace and
将其配置为永久跟踪并
span information actually it's just
跨越信息实际上只是
gonna perpetuate headers uu IDs that
将使标头uu ID永久存在
correspond to that and then that'll get
对应于此，然后得到
published out-of-band to something that
带外发布的东西
will then a get all of it into a big
然后将所有这些都变成一个大
picture well in the Zipkin world that
在Zipkin世界中很好地描绘出
might be Zipkin which runs off to the
可能是Zipkin，它跑到了
side connected through a broker in this
通过经纪人在这边连接
case it's not going to be Zipkin it'll
如果不是Zipkin，它将
be a stack driver trace so we're gonna
成为堆栈驱动程序跟踪，以便我们
use want to create a simple endpoint
使用想要创建一个简单的端点
here called the same client client okay
这里叫同一个客户
and our client code is just gonna call
我们的客户代码只是要调用
ourselves when we're gonna have a simple
自己，当我们要有一个简单的
endpoint that drive some traffic so I'm
导致一些流量的端点，所以我
gonna say actually they'll be multiple
要说实际上他们将是多个
responses let's do that okay return
回应让我们做得到
stream uh-oh ray alright so there's a
流吧，哦，雷，好吧，所以有一个
few names and what I'm going to do is
几个名字，我要做的是
I'm going to map each name into a
我将每个名称映射到一个
request that's gonna be sent over the
请求将通过
wire to myself okay to another end point
连线到我自己，可以到达另一个终点
in the same class so V though it is
在同一个班级，所以虽然V
giving it a name
给它起个名字
variable string name hello lady okay
可变字符串名称你好女士好
and we're gonna write a record here
我们要在这里写一张唱片
we're just create a record private final
我们只是创建一个创纪录的私人决赛
string call string name and we need the
字符串调用字符串名称，我们需要
rest of it problem so private
剩下的问题如此私密
the final best template and that's the
最终的最佳模板，那就是
constructor and here we'll say this dot
构造函数，在这里我们说这个点
rest template dot your entity HTTP your
其余模板点您的实体HTTP
localhost 8080 great name right it looks
看起来像localhost 8080的好名字
like okay and when you get the body
好像还可以，当你得到身体时
return that okay so let me say call for
还好吧，让我说呼吁
name and we want to do then is collect
名称，然后我们要做的就是收集
two lists
两张清单
okay so I'm just calling a bunch of name
好吧，我只是打个名字
I'm actually calling myself I'm just
我实际上是在称自己为
driving some traffic every time to make
每次都带来一些流量
calls client I'll Drive
打电话给我开车的客户
you know X number of records now each
您知道每个现在有X个记录
time that happens I want to also log
我想记录的发生时间
some information out to the console so
一些信息发送到控制台，所以
I'll stay logged that info and I'm ready
我将继续记录该信息，并准备就绪
is blog for day as well
也是一天的博客
[Applause]
[掌声]
okay so there's my simple configuration
好，那是我的简单配置
now in order for this to work I need to
为了使它正常工作，我现在需要
configure log4j to be aware of what's up
配置log4j以了解最新情况
okay that's a little that's actually
好吧，实际上是一点点
ought to be the most painful code that
应该是最痛苦的代码
we're gonna write for today because it's
我们今天要写，因为
XML and you know how much I love XML so
XML，您知道我有多爱XML
not my not very much right so let's see
不是我不是很正确，所以让我们看看
me we're gonna go to resources and play
我，我们要去玩玩
a file called me whoa easy easy a new
一个叫我的文件哇容易容易
file here called logged back springs XML
此处的文件称为Logged Back Springs XML
we're in with a pea configuration
我们有豌豆配置
to include every source might be easier
包括每个来源可能更容易
just copy and paste this one so me
只需复制并粘贴此一个，这样我
resources okay
资源还可以
I'm sure we have that one well so can I
我确定我们有一口井，所以我能
get it
得到它
well with our students by hand or
与我们的学生用手或
include resource equals or spring one
包括资源等于或弹簧一
boot log in log back instead XML Wow
启动登录重新登录，而不是XML Wow
okay easy I guess spring from a cloud
好吧，容易，我想是从云而来的春天
GCP Auto configure logging long back
GCP自动配置日志记录已久
okay so I'm just this is in the
好吧，我就是这个
documentation somewhere it's not
不在某处的文档
pleasant but it doesn't work and just
令人愉快，但它不起作用，只是
one of those things where you just gotta
这些事情之一，你必须
get right once and then you're fine and
一次做对，然后你就好了，
you're F equal over to left console okay
你等于左控制台了吗
and then what the stack divert okay
然后堆栈转移了什么
looks fine to me
对我来说很好
yeah yeah just go with that go ahead and
是的，只是继续前进，
try it we start
试试我们开始
oops
哎呀
oh that's the routines of logging so
哦，这是记录的例程，所以
this is exception that's now there we're
这是一个例外，我们现在在那里
going it that should go in so now
去吧，应该现在就去
right forget you can see it says
对吧，忘了你可以看到它说
Holloway hello Dave hello Bob hello Paul
Holloway你好Dave你好Bob你好Paul
okay so a bunch of names that we got
好吧，我们得到了一堆名字
back we can see that it's got the trace
回来，我们可以看到它的踪迹
and span context and indication of
和跨度上下文和指示
whether that request has been traced or
该请求是否已被跟踪或
not right the probability set at one dot
设置一个点的概率不正确
o was 100% that's indicative of the fact
o是100％表示事实
that it's a trace that request and we
这是要求的痕迹，我们
can now go here and go to the trace
现在可以去这里去追踪
overview and we can see recent traces
概述，我们可以看到最近的痕迹
put on this and there we go so if I
穿上这个，我们走了，如果我
click on this I can see that I greeted
点击这个我可以看到我打招呼
ray and then I greeted a bunch of others
雷，然后我向其他人打招呼
I can see the request and the response
我可以看到请求和响应
request respond request response right
请求响应请求响应权
and even better since we have the
甚至更好，因为我们有
logging starter for stackdriver trace I
为stackdriver trace I记录启动程序
can actually click on show logs and now
可以实际点击显示日志，现在
I can see the logs that correlate with
我可以看到与之相关的日志
time that these messages were for traced
这些消息被追踪的时间
right greetings ray Green's Dave reading
正确的问候雷·格林的戴夫读书
Bob reading Paul Green Canyon green Kim
鲍勃读保罗·格林峡谷·格林·金
negating etc isn't that cool I think
否定等等不是很酷
it's really just nice and I've got the
真的很好，我已经
context associated with each request
与每个请求关联的上下文
here as well does that do
在这里也这样做
oh that's nice - look at that I think I
哦，那很好-看，我想我
prefer the other way but either way
更喜欢另一种方式
that's cool so my friend we've looked at
太酷了，所以我看过我的朋友
just a few things you can do you can do
您可以做的几件事就可以做
with Google Cloud
使用Google Cloud
I've only of course begun to scratch the
我当然只是开始抓
surface we looked at boring things like
表面上我们看着无聊的东西
my sequel you know unique Google scale
我的续集，您知道独特的Google规模
things like spanner we looked at api's
像扳手一样的东西，我们看了api的
aren't directly supported by a spring
没有弹簧直接支撑
but are interesting and are accessible
但很有趣并且可以访问
now that there now that the
现在那里现在
authentication is handled for you in the
身份验证在
sort of convenient way like the Google
像Google这样的便捷方式
vision API we looked at integration and
视觉API，我们研究了集成和
messaging and then we looked at
消息，然后我们看了看
observability and how that's supported
可观察性及其支持方式
by the stack driver suite of tools in
由工具中的堆栈驱动程序套件
Google Cloud so you know a lot of good
Google Cloud让您知道很多好处
stuff here just a lot of good stuff in
这里的东西很多
the the spring integration for Google
Google的春季整合
Cloud and of course there's more on the
云，当然还有更多
way
方式
I certainly think these things are
我当然认为这些事情是
compelling and obviously they make a
引人注目的，显然他们使
great pairing with something like a
与诸如
Cloud Foundry because there you can run
Cloud Foundry，因为您可以在那里运行
your apps the easiest most concise way
您的应用程序最简单，最简洁的方式
possible and then take advantage and
可能然后利用
feel free to take advantage and fully
随时利用并充分利用
exploit the things that make the
利用使
platform valuable so with that my
平台很有价值，因此我
friends with that as always thank you so
一如既往的朋友谢谢你
much for watching and we'll see you next
收看很多，我们下次见
time
时间
you
您